<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>测试 on Hoshino&#39;s Grocery</title>
        <link>https://hoshino.github.io/en/categories/%E6%B5%8B%E8%AF%95/</link>
        <description>Recent content in 测试 on Hoshino&#39;s Grocery</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hoshino.github.io/en/categories/%E6%B5%8B%E8%AF%95/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>First article</title>
        <link>https://hoshino.github.io/en/p/first-article/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://hoshino.github.io/en/p/first-article/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-on-earth-do-i-want-to-say&#34;&gt;What on earth do I want to say?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for why we build a blog, it may be that the teacher assigned a website imitating others to write a web page when learning the front end a year ago. I saw some bloggers&amp;rsquo; blog interfaces are very beautiful, which deeply attracted me, so I thought I would do one myself. I even want to move forward in the future. But later I saw that many people on the Internet said that doing the front-end was as tired and less expensive as moving bricks on the construction site. This made me a little confused. When I was doing a project last semester, the teacher asked me what &amp;ldquo;position&amp;rdquo; I planned to do, and I replied that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t considered it yet. I&amp;rsquo;m still struggling with front-end or back-end. But later, when the class was almost divided, he asked me, &amp;ldquo;just be the back end, okay?&amp;rdquo; I said yes. Later, when choosing the direction, I also chose the back end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for why, I also thought that for a period of time, I was the kind of person who lacked creativity. Even if I was skilled in adjusting styles and understanding various animation effects, I might not be able to use them well. Blog is also, in fact, the most important thing of blog is the content, and the interface should be secondary. However, at the level of the penultimate Chinese score in my middle school class, I feel there is nothing to write, so it has been shelved for a long time. But recently, I found that many programmers will record their methods and feelings of solving vulnerabilities on Blog websites, so I still did this blog according to the tutorial.
to be continue&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
